- Add rand numbers to client in userlist and remove for client user selection
- Make sure client properly sends message, maybe server returns confirmation and client tries again after timeout - 3 tries and it stops
- use pyinstaller to package - add directions 

- Use threads to keep both listening for datagrams while still running code to handle user input or send msgs 


- Add print statements to server and an interface to client for viewing users, changing users, and sending messages or checking inbox
